Caleb Riley

214-926-7002 riley.caleb21@gmail.com

Summary

I am a hard worker with a passion for construction, business, sales and fitness. I have extensive experience in crew management, supervising construction, demolition, haul off, jobsite cleanup, customer service, equipment maintenance, logistics, inventory control and product sales. I am a versatile supervisor with strong leadership skills to organize and motivate a team to deliver a top-quality outcome.

Experience

Faber Site Services, Dallas, TX Crew Chief Supervisor, 2019 – present

Manages all aspects of the job site from selecting crew, assigning tasks and loading proper equipment according to construction needs. Corresponds and works with client to achieve an aesthetically pleasing design for their project objective.

- Identifies and documents issues to ensure job is handled correctly, assuring insurance & client are aware.
- Mediates between client and outside businesses. Examples: Service Master, Servpro, Prime Reconstruction...
- Manages budget by creating a time frame, equipment list and crew that will complete the project.
- Organizes and maintains use of machinery and equipment.
- Problem solving for unexpected circumstances.
- Prioritize high standard job site cleanup according to situation.
- Flexible skills set. Examples: Leading crew to build and repair fences, concrete installation, landscaping...

Ader Sporting Goods, Dallas, TX Marketing Sales Representative, 2017 – 2020

Responsible for athletic equipment sales for the Ader Sporting Goods Company. Had a loyal clientele following as well and networked new sales on a regular basis.

- Post products on various platforms Ebay, Offerup, Newegg.
- Negotiate pricing with new and existing clients.
- Perform market research for up-to-date pricing of desired goods.
- Manage information, appointments and meetings with clients using Microsoft software.
- Designed and created the company showroom to allow clients to experience various products available.
- Strategize social media marketing per demand of hot products. Created best practices to stay on trend and product focused.
- Modeled merchandise for Ader Sporting Goods social media and other platforms.

Catalyst Equipment, Plano, TX Sales & Customer Service Representative, 2006 – 2017

Responsible for the Semiconductor equipment sales, marketing and shipping. Worked closely with owner to assure quality experience for the customer, domestic and international level.

- Online sales/marketing utilizing Ebay and Dynaprice.
- Perform market research for up-to-date pricing of desired goods.
- Negotiate with Ebay customers on product prices and manage Ebay customer service.
- Manipulate data in Excel for Mailchimp to send out to customer list.
- Communicate with logistic companies to deliver sold products to customers.

Education

Sam Houston University, Huntsville, TX Bachelor of Business Administration, General Business